Welcome, friend. Today I'll show you the new and best way of creating consistent AI influencers that not only look real
But also can hold your product and lip sync to your voice. Take a look at these
So I'm gonna try one of these David protein bars and this thing has 20 grams of protein
I'm not even kidding. This is probably one of the better protein bars. I've seen this is an in-depth tutorial for those who want to create
Contents for their brand or their clients the only YouTube tutorial you'll ever need
I'm going to show you an entirely new pipeline and you are going to walk away with a few things today
One, you'll know exactly how to create AI influencers or characters
Two, you will learn how to have them hold any product
Three, you'll learn how to clone their voice and keep it consistent
Four, you'll learn how to generate infinitely long talking videos that go beyond 15 second mark
Five, you learn how to place your influencers into specific environments, so let's get started creating your influencer
There are two ways of creating your influencer. Number one, you use yourself for an existing human with real IP
And number two, you create an influencer from scratch that does not exist and you create that IP
So let's start with number one so that you can understand the flow
I want to have myself sell product online and I want to create a bunch of ads
So I want to scale my own creative output in my company and I want to be the spokesperson for the brand
I'm going to use this image of myself and inside nano banana two
I'll generate five new shots almost like a live book or a character sheet
So we're going to head over to image editor inside enhancer and make sure that we are using nano banana two
We're going to select 2k resolution which is more than enough and we're going to choose 16 by 9 aspect ratio
This is important. We are creating a character rotation sheets and to do that
We will use this prompt that you are seeing on the screen. You can screenshot that
Essentially what this prompt does is that it takes the uploaded image as the main identity reference
And it tells the model to keep the the person's core look consistent
Meaning that the phase of proportions of body to shape the hair that the overall vibe should still feel like the same person
Then the prompt asks the model to reformat that into something that looks like a professional design board on a white background
Instead of a normal portrait so rather than generating one random new image
It's going to build a structured sheet that shows the character from multiple angles
This is very important especially on what we're going to be doing today
So this is the prompt can take your time to read through it
You can also find this prompt in the guide in the link in the description
So we're going to base a prompt inside nano banana two make sure that we have uploaded your reference image and hit generate and this is what we get
This is our base image. Okay, so this is a source reference, and this is what it showed me
Essentially, it's me through different views. It's pretty cool
We will download this and we're going to generate four more shots
But first we will create a duplicate of this image and crop it so it only focuses on the front the side and the back view
So these three views that you are seeing on screen you can either screenshot it or you can
Crop it to match the framing accordingly and once you have this frame that you're seeing right now
We're going to head over again into nano banana. We're going to replace our source image
Which was this one originally we're going to upload our new cropped shot and we're going to ask it to give you a close-up of the character's
Features very simple will say give me a close-up of this man
Focusing on his facial features. So almost like a headshot. We're going to hit generate
We're going to keep everything as is and boom. This is our image number two. Crazy. It looks like me
So we're going to download this and we're going to save that now onto image number three
We need a full body shot
We're going to keep the same reference image and we will change the prompt and ask nano banana to give us a full body shot instead
So I will say give me a full body shot and make sure that the face is clear very simple nothing complicated here
We don't have to write like all these extremely long detail prompts. You do not need that
So we're going to hit generate and boom. This is what we get this is our image number three image number four
Using the same references before nothing is changing. We will generate a close-up shot of the side profile
So we will say give me a close-up shot of his site profile left and right that's it
That's the prompt don't ever think that hit generate look at the consistency look at the details here and last
We need an extreme close-up of the features
So now we're going to be using this images our source reference and we will ask nano banana to
Give me a grid of close-up shots of the men's feature such as the eyes the lips the nose the lashes the brow
Okay, this is the prompt and again make sure to replace the source reference accordingly
This is our new source reference for image number five our last image hit generate and boom. This is what we get
This is very very impressive now
Let's zoom out we have five pictures of the character in this case myself and we will use this for the rest of this tutorial
This is step number one creating the data set for your character and in this case the character is me a real human
Now you can do the same exact thing for your AI influencer that does not exist except that there's an extra step at the beginning
So generating that base image the rest of the steps remain unchanged
So here's what I like to do to generate my character because I believe that this is the most realistic way of generating results
That look real source image is extremely important and right now it's more important than prompting to do that
I'm going to head over into kora over here
And I'm going to select kora reality which is a fine tuned version of z image that's passing through
Just recently when 2.7 was just released a few days ago with
Laura's this is too technical if you're not building with AI
You don't really have to worry about it
I want you to paste this prompt and change it accordingly to your character specifications
You can change the input the values such as the age the style of the frame in the background etc
So this is the problem that you're seeing on the screen. We're going to select the 9 by 16 as our aspect ratio
The age that you find and we're going to hit generate boom
This is what we got look at this hyper realistic base image of the influencer
I can edit this with nano banana 2 if I wish or our own full access and henser editing model
For now, I'll keep this as is I like it and now that we have our base image
We can repeat the other steps that we mentioned before to create the character sheet
So this is our base image and this is the entire character sheet that I've created with it
I don't want to be repetitive great now. Let the fun begin
It's time to bring our AI influencer to live
Let's give her her name. I'm going to call her Sam and in order to bring Sam to life
We have to head over to video generator and we're going to select cdense 2 and we can use either our multi reference feature or our
UGC feature the UGC feature allows you to generate a UGC style video based on
One influencer image only one while the multi reference mode
allows you to to upload multiple images first
Let's create our UGC ad. We're going to head over to UGC and in here
We will upload one character image and you can even be the first image
That we generated with kora if you prefer and we will upload our product image though
This one over here and we're going to write a simple prompt to test us out
You can check out this other tutorial to learn more about how to prompt for different UGC use cases
Or again, you can check out the guide that's attached in the comments
So this is the prompt that I'm going to be using
Can read this you can screenshot it. I want to use my influencer to hold the protein bar
I'm not affiliated with David protein bar. I wish they can sponsor me
I've never tried it to be honest with you
But I think that it looks very cool the branding is nice
Now let's make sure that in the prompt you are adding what you want your influencer to say
This is very important. So this part. This is what my influencer is saying and after pacing the prompt
Select 9x16 aspect ratio and hit
Generates boom. This is what we get. Look at this. I'm not even kidding
This is probably one of the better protein bars. I've seen
28 grams of protein
150 calories and zero sugar. That's actually kind of ridiculous
And chocolate chip cookie dough. Yeah, I'd eat this again. Okay, wait this actually shocked me
This has 28 grams of protein only 150 calories and zero sugar
Like how is that even real and it's chocolate chip cookie dough flavored too. I'm sorry. This is kind of insane
Wait, this is actually wild. This bar has 28 grams of protein
Only 150 calories and zero grams of sugar and it's it's chocolate chip cookie dough flavored
That's honestly kind of insane. I love it look at the details and look at the text rendering look at the emotional delivery
Now there's a reason that we generated the character sheet
Okay, and you might be asking why the hell did we do this in the first place if we are not even using it
We will do it right now
The ugc case is different from what let's say cinematic commercials
Maybe you don't want to create a ugc type video you want to create a cool commercial
And this is where our character sheet comes in you need multiple inputs
So cDens can understand your character three dimensionally and to do that instead of using the ugc
Feature we're going to head over to the multi-reference feature
And we will upload our five images of our character and
One product image and we're going to drop it in this prompt
I really want to get a cool short commercial about this protein bar
I go over the prompt formula in this guide and I'm going to do so in the next video
All you have to worry about right now is copy the prompt and maybe go to clawed or gbt to adapt it based on your use case
It's the easiest thing that you can do we're going to select 16 by 9 aspect ratio the pro model 15 seconds and we're going to hit generate boom
This is what we get watch
In the cold only the strong remain
David
Long night sharp choice David
When pressure hits this is what holds David very
Impressive this would have cost thousands of dollars traditionally look at the consistency. It's nothing like I've ever seen
Honestly a grade we have a character that's holding the product consistent and all that
How do we keep the voice right? That's one of the questions that everyone asks
They're simple instead of using my AI influencer. I'm going to use my character now as a reference
So I'm going to use this all these five images
Still in the multi-reference feature. We're going to upload myself and
We're going to upload this is important a sixth second high quality audio of yourself speaking
This is my audio and wait for it
You can use your own voice and have the actor lip sync and drive the entire generation around your words
And after uploading that we need to do two things
We need to make sure that whenever c-dens generates a footage
It references our voice and it clones it
And also we have to make sure that we are writing what we are saying in the video two crucial aspects of this
Okay
So to do that we need to paste in this line at the beginning
And at the end of our prompts always and in the middle
We're going to put in our main description and make sure that we have a lip syncing line or multiple lip syncing lines
Where we say exactly what the character will be speaking
But this is the final prompt can copy this here are all the source references that we have uploaded
We have our five images of our character we have our audio and then we have our product and we're going to hit generate
Look at this
So I'm going to try one of these David protein bars and this thing has 20 grams of protein
And it is so good like guys you should try this out before they sell out because I don't know how long they're going to last
It sounds like me right
It's very impressive guys
Here are some more examples hey stop stop
Hey, hey man
I'm I'm sorry. I'm sorry about this
But I would really love for you to tell me how the hell you're keeping up with all these AI tools because this is insane
Now how do we actually make the video
Longer while keeping the same voice and style simple we're going to use the same method
But this time we will use only one reference image instead of an entire concept sheet
So we're going to grab our last frame of this video like right we want to extend this video
And we're going to use this free site that I've built so you can extract your last frame
So upload your video click on extract frames and get your last frame downloaded
Head over to multi reference mode again
We are using multi reference here to to make the video longer
And we need to paste in these lines
First line about the audio that we've talked about
And second align about how it should reference the exact image and background as our source
So it should be exactly the same as this one
That's the line that we're going to use this is to help multi reference not hallucinate because usually in multi reference
What happens is that you upload a source and it's going to think about that reference in different contexts
Not necessarily use that as the first frame so the likelihood of your character being in different environments
Is high now you might ask why not just use image to video right is going to keep our first frame consistent
And then we can start expanding from there
Well, if you do so fortunately you cannot upload audio reference
Therefore, it's not going to work now this for now is the best way that you can do it
And will probably change the next few weeks but for now this is what we got
We're going to hit generate and boom look at that and I swear this is not sponsored
I wish David sponsored me for all this free marketing
But hey, you can't always win
So I'm going to try one of these David protein bars and this thing has 20 grams of protein and it is so good
Like guys you should try this out before they sell out because I don't know how long they're going to last
And I swear this is not sponsored
I wish David sponsored me for all this free marketing
But hey, you can't always win
Now it might not flow very well
But as we know cuts are part of content creation as a format
Perfect, so we'll learn how to create our influencers
How to have them speak insistently
But how do we add this influencer into a particular scene
Following the same logic the only thing that we need to do here now is add a background image as a reference
And we're going to reference that background in our prompt
For example, this is Joe Robins background
And I want to generate a podcast talking video of my character as a guest there
And all I have to do is describe the setting and ask it to reference and place the actor
In the background shown by mentioning the file in the prompt
All you do is add and your image number
Now you can also go ahead and you can describe the background if needed
But this is my prompt you can screenshot that
We're going to hit generate boom
David
This is the David protein bar
It has 28 grams of protein
My friend this is only the tip of the iceberg
There's so much more that you can do
And in the next video I'll show you how to create cinematic commercials
Like this one that I've created from one single prompt
We'll go over the problem, the structure
How to build it yourself
So turn on the notifications
Hit that like and subscribe button because it helps not only me
But also other people find this type of content
Everything that you saw today is available right now inside enhancer
Available everywhere
With more updates and features coming soon for you to try
If you want more prompt formulas like the ones that I showed you today
And if you want to learn more about how to actually build a product
Like the agent or the UGC on top of cDense2 for your own clients
Come join my free community it's called public AI
The link is in the description as well
It is completely free
And again here's a part I'm most excited to tell you
Because right now inside public AI we are running a pilot
Where my team is helping five students build five real SAS apps
Full-time AI, stack engineers working on projects
Four, three
We literally assign engineers to your ideas
And we help you build it even if it's from scratch
We draw every month there's a real interest
And if you have an idea and you just want to throw your name in
Join in the community
Apply
Worst case you will learn a ton from everyone else building in there
And the best case my team will build the product for you
If this video was useful to you
Hit that like button
It sounds small but it genuinely helps other people find this kind of content
And that means a lot to me
Now links for everything are in the description
I'm going to see you in the next one
And do not forget my friend create without limits
Because you can
This is Syria